<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SlayinMuzos</string>
    <string name= "gameMode">Game Mode</string>
    <string name= "tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name= "vikingTutorial">Recursive, the Viking</string>
    <string name= "slimeTutorial">SliMuzos, the Slimes Monsters</string>
    <string name= "leftRightTutorial">Left and Right</string>
    <string name= "jumpTutorial">Jump to Dodge</string>
    <string name= "alertTitle">Exit the game</string>
    <string name= "alertMsg">Are you sure to quit the game?</string>
    <string name= "yes">Yes</string>
    <string name= "no">No</string>
    <string name= "normalMode">Normal</string>
    <string name= "madnessMode">Madness</string>
    <string name= "leader">Score</string>
    <string name= "back">Back Menu</string>
    <string name= "scoreList">SCORE LIST</string>
    <string name= "slayinMuzos">SLAYIN MUZOS</string>
    <string name= "vikingDesc">Recursive, the Viking, descends from a huge line of hunters of SlimeMuzos. Help him eliminate all possible SliMuzos.
        \n\nA Cermuzo once said, the recursion is wonderful.\n\nThat is the reason why my parents called me that name.\n\n - Recursive, the viking. </string>
    <string name= "slimeDesc">The SliMuzos are a race created by the wise sorcerers Cermuzos many years ago.
        \n\nThey are gel, elusive and somewhat silly, but their evolution allowed the Cermuzos to reproduce their fanaticism towards Michael Jackson, so the SliMuzos sometimes make a moonwalk while they walk.</string>
    <string name= "buttonDesc">You are locked in a dungeon, you only have three options, two of them is running side by side like a programmer running from a NullPointerException.
        \n\nIf you press left, you will go to the left, and if you press right, then to the right.</string>
    <string name= "buttonsJumpDesc">You have another option, jump and dodge the SliMuzos, they are idiots, they dont know what it is to jump and they try to imitate you when they collide with the wall, yet they are not able to predict your agile movement.
        \n\nI have nothing left but to teach you about movements, eliminate them all with your damn sword you son of a beach.</string>

</resources>
